but then I'm on my way already
is debt
I'm going to São Paulo now
even sent me a car
want to go with me no
what a pity I work
what a pity you work
Juninho you are naughty
Juninho
I got this one you're following the series anyway
what day is today
eighty-four
look at your Cara mano day 85
I got that call there
oh all right
this is Polly da Cora
we here from Cora
I wanted to invite you to tell this whole story
for our lord Igor
in our studio you are so participating with us
I don't think you have a lot to contribute.
guy look at that crazy thing
I'm going to exchange an idea with the bank owner now
here in san Paulo
thank you
I know people see
merry christmas
happy new year
stay with god brother
when you create your own box
you start to attract attention from people man
and then opportunities like this appear
like this
you
ok Cara
ha i didn't say anything to you about how the championship went
because the link will actually come up
I promise to send
but believes that the Cora bank
you're also interested in my beatbox man
that's a good part
way you think it might be interesting
without killing its authenticity
as soon as the link to the conversation comes out I'll post it for you
took a while
no case
the car will
that's it monday
O I fall Monday
my friend
monday
ten o'clock in the morning
the car is available in the store
it's in the hand
ready